欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
鳕鱼角 前情提要
Previously on Hightown
你尿检大麻阳性
You tested positive for marijuana.
-你不再是这个组的一员了  -操你妈
You're off the unit. Fuck this, man.
你要是有更好的货卖 那带我一个啊
You have better coke to sell, sign me up.
我是瑞秋
I'm Rachel.
如果有需要的话 随时找我
Let me know if you ever need some help.
嗨 瑞秋 我妈把你的号码给我了
Hi, Rachel. Got your number from my mom.
或许你明天早上可以帮我看下孩子吗
Maybe you could babysit tomorrow morning.
我的天 我做到了 成功了
Oh, my God, I did it. It worked.
你太棒了
You're amazing.
-你熟这姑娘吗  -她叫维罗妮卡
- You know this girl? - Her name is Veronica.
我从斯韦齐那儿认识她的
I met her through Swayzee.
赶紧滚 臭婊子
Get the fuck out, bitch!
斯韦齐 什么情况
Swayzee, what is happening?
艾玛 我得跟你聊聊 艾玛
Emma, I need to talk to you. Emma.
这就是我们的新目标 肖恩和欧文·弗劳利
These are our new targets: Shane and Owen Frawley.
奥西托一直在给弗劳利叔侄供货
Osito was supplying the Frawleys
直到我们除掉纽约的毒贩
until we took out New York.
远离我的地盘 不然就开战
Back the fuck off my blocks, or there's gonna be war.
给我放清醒点 我们要开战了
Get your shit together. We're going to war.
现在我抓到你袭警
I got you for assaulting a police officer.
我们菲茨会把你介绍给欧文的好兄弟雷德
Fitzy here is gonna introduce you to Owen's boy Red.
我是来问维罗妮卡的事情
Came here to ask about Veronica.
-干什么 你他妈是条子啊  -不是
- Why? Are you a fucking cop? - No.
可怜的维罗妮卡
Poor Veronica.
太悲伤了
So sad.
我想了很多关于你的事
♪ Ithoughta lot ofthings Aboyt you ♪
♪ I thought a lot of things About you ♪
我想了很多关于你的事
♪'I thought a lot of things About you ♪
我睡不着 只想着你
♪ I stayed awake ♪ust thinking about you ♪
♪ Istayed awake ♪ust thinking about you ♪
我睡不着 只想着你
但现在我离开了
♪ But now I'm away ♪
你必须得留下
♪ You had to stay ♪
♪ You had to stay ♪'
明天属于我
♪ Tomorrow's a day of mine ♪
不再有你
♪ That you won't be in ♪
我也想说我只是在享受生活
♪ I tried to say I was just having fun ♪
♪'〔tried to say 〔wasjusthaving fun ♪'
但我知道你就是对的那个
♪ But Ireally knew That you were the one ♪
♪ But I really knew That you were the one ♪
但我知道你就是对的那个
♪'But Ireally knew That you were the one ♪'
现在我走了
♪And now that I'm gone ♪
我知道我错了
♪I see I was wrong ♪
我早该明白的
♪ Ishould have known AlI along ♪
♪ I should have known All along ♪
时间会证明一切
♪ That time would tell ♪
离开你一周时间
♪ A week without you ♪
我应该要忘记
♪ I should forget ♪
♪ Ishould forget ♪
我应该要忘记
♪ I should forget ♪
离开你两周时间
♪ Two weeks without you ♪'
我还在想着你说的话
♪ And I'm still thinking about The things that you said ♪
假期 依然可爱
♪ Vacation just another love- in ♪
假期 希望你能爱我
♪ Vacation I hope you love me ♪
假期 你能念着我吗
♪ Vacation Would you think of me? ♪
我觉得我要不告而别
♪ I think I'll leave Without saying goodbye ♪
♪I think I'll leave Without saying goodbye ♪
我觉得我要不告而别
♪ Ithink IlHeave Without saying goodbye ♪
我觉得你知道为什么
♪ I think that you know The reason why ♪
要是我留下呢
♪ What if I was to stay? ♪
事情是否会不一样
Would things turn out Some other way?
反正我也不会知道了
♪ I'lI never know anyway ♪
你不知道
♪ You don't really know ♪
自己惹上了什么事
♪ What you got yourself into ♪
你觉得自己知道
♪ Boy, you think you know ♪
但事情没有那么简单
♪ But it just ain't That simple ♪
我没有时间
♪ I don't got the time ♪-
你应该体会言外之意
♪You should Read between the lines ♪
因为你现在翻页太快
♪'Cause you're skimming Through the pages ♪
看上去真的很危险
♪ It's really looking Dangerous ♪
你不知道自己
♪ You don't really know what you got...♪
我想去游个泳
I want to take a swim.
我想看着你游泳
I want to watch you take a swim.
我没有时间
♪ I don't got the time ♪
你应该体会言外之意
♪You should read Between the lines ♪
因为你现在翻页太快
♪Cause you're skimming Through the pages ♪
看上去真的很危险
♪ It's really looking Dangerous, this ♪
我开着你的车时
♪ When Im driving In your car ♪
感觉自己无所不能
♪ Make me feel like I could do anything ♪
但我没有动力
♪But I do not have The drive ♪
我渴求着你的速度
♪ I'm in desperate need Of your speed ♪
你的速度
♪ Of your speed ♪
我开着你的车时
♪Oh, when Im driving In your car ♪
感觉自己无所不能
♪' Make me feeH ike I could do anything ♪
但我没有时间
♪'ButIdo not have the time ♪
我渴求着你的速度
♪ I'm in desperate need Of your speed ♪
你的速度
♪ Of your speed ♪
♪Of your speed ♪
维罗妮卡
Veronica?
Veronica!
我觉得你是
- - I think you were, uh,
做了个怪梦之类的
having, like, a weird dream or something.
靠 抱歉 我不是有意要睡着的
Shit, I'm sorry. I didn't mean to fall asleep.
只是
It's just, uh...
你为什么要说可怜的维罗妮卡
...why did you say"poor ∨eronica"?
我没这么说过
I didn't say that.
你能不能告诉我 我去哪儿能找到她
Can you just tell me where I can find her?
想得美 但我才不会把朋友的信息
Nice try, but I don't really give my friends' info out
随便给陌生人
to random fucking strangers.
听着 不是你想的那样 艾玛
Look, it's not like that, Emma.
我们一起疯狂嗨了一个周末
We had a crazy weekend together,
我醒过来的时候 她开着我的车跑了
and when I came to, she had taken off with my car.
这听上去确实像是我姐妹会干的事儿
I mean, that does sound like my girl.
不是 我不是气她开走了我的车 好吗
No, I'm not pissed about the car, all right?
就是
It's just that
我找回车的时候
...when I got it back,
在车上发现了她的衣服
I found her shirt in it,
上面都他妈是血
all fucking bloody.
老天
Jesus.
是啊 我知道
Yeah, I know
所以我很害怕
and I'm scared.
你听好了
Here's the thing.
维罗妮卡·莱瓦伊是能管好自己的
Veronica Levoie can handle herself.
听着 我知道这听起来很疯狂
Look, I know this sounds crazy,
但我真的需要确定她人没事
but Ineed to know that she's okay.
求你了
Please.
我得见见她 如果她没事 那一切都好
I need to get eyes on her. If she's good, then fine.
但如果不是 我得帮她
But if not, I have to help her.
行 那我给她打电话 行了吧
Okay, I'll call her. Okay?
谢谢你
Thank you.
她肯定是忘记付手机费了
She must've forgot to pay her phone bill or something.
你能不能直接带我去她住的地方呢
Okay, well, can you just take me to where she lives?
我靠 姐 我真服了
Damn, bitch. God.
没人教过你求人要怎么说吗
Did no one ever teach you the magic fucking word?
-拜托了  -不是 另一个
- Please? - Uh- uh, the other one.
钱
Money.
我昨晚那两百块没拿到 所以
I never did get that$200 from last night, so...
成交
Deal.
所以 弗兰基的律师准备在交叉质询的时候
So, Frankie's lawyer likes to take a lead pipe
狠狠打击控方
to the prosecution during cross- examination.
这我们早就知道了
This we know.
是 我需要人帮忙给证人做准备
Yeah, I could use a little help prepping a witness.
当然可以 但我已经开始
Of course, but I already started
帮排骨做准备了
working with Chuleta on that.
我说的不是排骨
Not talking about Chuleta.
请坐 警探
Take a seat, Sergeant.
你应该也清楚 弗兰基最好的办法就是
As you know, impugning the state's witnesses
攻击控方证人可信度 所以我们需要你做好准备
is Frankie's best strategy, so we need you to be ready.
我不是没上过证人席
You know I've been on the stand before.
好吧 这样 也行
Okay, you know what? Fine.
那就赶紧完事儿 我还有工作要做
Let's get it over with. I got work to do.
警察工作 还记得是干什么吗
Police work. Remember what that is?
抓坏人的
Catching the bad guys? -
那行吧
Okay, then.
你是什么时候开始和弗兰基·奎瓦斯的未婚妻上床的
When did you start having sex with Frankie Cuevas'fiancee?
不好意思 你说什么
Im sorry. What?
你觉得卡莱尔会放过这一点吗
You think Carlisle's not asking that question?
那你让他问 你提出反对
Well, you let him ask that, and then you object,
不就结束了吗
and we move on.
我会提出反对的 但法官会判定反对无效
I'll object, the judge will overrule,
然后你就要被迫回答了
and you'll be forced to answer.
你必须得回答
You're gonna have to answer questions
关于你和蕾妮·塞格纳之间性关系的问题的
about your sexual relationship with Renee Segna.
-行吧  -你还跟自己的哪些线人
Fine. Which of your other CIs
上过床
did you have sex with?
没有了
None of them.
雪莉·亨利也没有吗
Not Sherri Henry?
雪莉·亨利也没有
No, not Sherri Henry.
我想知道这是谁告诉你的
I want to know who told you that.
是他吗
Was it him?
要回答问题的人不是我
I'm not the one answering questions here.
都是鬼扯 你知道这是什么吗
This is bullshit You know what this is?
这是我和他之间的私仇
Personal bullshit between me and him.
你就一点压力都受不了是吧
You just can't take the heat, can you?
-我就是压力里生下来的  -交给我艾伦
I was born in the heat. - Ive got this, Alan.
这跟我们的事儿没关系
This is not about us.
这是为了弗兰基·奎瓦斯
It's about Frankie Cuevas.
他的律师肯定会说
His lawyer is gonna say you threw it
你和弗兰基的脱衣舞娘女友搞上了
at Frankie's stripper girlfriend,
搞大了她的肚子
knocked her up,
然后无中生有陷害了他
and then cooked up some bullshit case
就为了娶她
to make an honest woman out of her.
他会把你描述成色欲熏心的马克·福尔曼
He's gonna paint you as Mark Fuhrman with a hard- on
如果这成功了 他被无罪释放
And if it works, if he walks.
那这就又他妈是你的过错 雷
...it's on your fucking shoulders, Ray, again.
你他妈有什么资格这么说
Who the fuck are you to talk like that? Look- -
你他妈会付出代价的 雷
You're gonna pay the fucking bill, Ray.
好了 够了 够了
AlI right, enough. Enough.
这次是我错了
This was a mistake.
雷 我们下次再聊
Ray, you and I will be talking again.
-不带他  -是 不带他
Without himYes, without him,
但你得习惯这些
but get used to this.
弗兰基·奎瓦斯是个杀人凶手
Frankie Cuevas is a killer.
我们永远也不可能知道他到底杀了多少人
He's got more bodies on him than we'll ever know.
他才是坏人
He's the bad guy.
是他
It's him.
咱们单刀直入
♪ Let's get straight to it ♪
废话不多说直接动手
♪ Ain't tryin'to talk Let's do it ♪
我们开枪扫射
♪, we shootin'♪
大获成功 他们节节败退
♪The opps be sick They losin'♪
我们手里这些枪 都用上
♪ All these guns we got We use'em ♪
他被抓了 那小鬼是傻的
♪ He got caught That boy was stupid ♪
枪被记录了 快点搞把新的
♪ Gun got dirty, hurry up Get a new one ♪
你不会想过多纠缠的
♪, you don't wanna Get into it ♪
咱们单刀直入
♪ Let's get straight to it ♪
废话不多说 直接动手
♪Ain't tryin' to talk Let's do it ♪
举止疯狂 四处扫射
♪ play crazy In this bitch, we shootin'♪
大获成功 他们节节败退
♪The opps be sick They losin' ♪
我们手里这些枪 都用上
♪ All these guns we got We use'em ♪
他被抓了 那小鬼是傻的
♪ He got caught That boy was stupid ♪
枪被记录了 快点搞把新的
♪ Gun got dirty, hurry up Get a new one ♪
你不会想过多纠缠的
♪, you don't wanna Get into it...♪
你有什么要说的吗 小鬼
You got something to say, boy?
没错 就是这样
Yeah, that's it
去找爸爸吧 小婊子
Run to papi, you little bitch.
怎么了
What's up?
老兄 白人有动作了
Bro, white boys is up and runningl
谁
Who?
香草大猩猩
Vanilla Gorilla
绝对是准备搞大动作
definitely got a whole storefront up.
我跟他们说了 如果冒犯我们 会有什么后果
I told them what happened if they stepped to us.
那他们确实冒犯了
Um, they stepped.
好 这事儿交给我和幸运
All right, well, me and Lucky are on it.
放机灵点 小心报复
Keep your head up. Figure for some blowback.
好 没问题
AlI right. Bet
就像我们想的一样
It's like we thought.
就是白人搞的
White boys is the ones that's doing it.
现在我们得弄清楚 他们是怎么做的
Now we gotta figure out how they doing it.
你看看那儿
Check it.
去看看咱能看见些什么
Let's see what we can see.
我马上来 瑞秋
Be right there, Rachel.
-嗨  -嗨 蕾妮
- Hey. Hey, Renee.
你在等人吗
Expecting someone?
新保姆
A new babysitter.
对哦 你们有新宝宝了
That's right. You guys got a new addition.
恭喜
Congratulations.
雷去上班了
Ray's at work.
其实我是来找你的
Well, um, actually, I'm here to see you.
地方检察官让我来找你
Well, the DA asked me to reach out.
地方检察官
DA?
为什么
For what?
帮你准备上庭
Getting you ready for trial.
说好的不是这样的
That wasn't part of the deal.
我从来没答应过会作证指证弗兰基
I never said I'd testify against Frankie.
我们是想帮你准备好
We want to get you ready in case, uh,
万一他的律师给你打电话
his lawyer gives you a call.
弗兰基可能会想要你为他作证
Frankie may want you to testify for him
证明关于你和雷之间关系的开始
about the beginnings of the relatjonship for you and Ray.
不 不可能 而且我 我没有义务作证
No. No way, and I don't- I don't have to testify.
我有豁免权
I have immunity.
其实 这种豁免权会导致
Well, actually, immunity revokes
你不能行使沉默权
your Fifth Amendment rights.
你和雷得聊聊
You and Ray need to talk.
你需要准备好面对一切可能
You should be ready for what's coming.
行吧 我会联系她的
Fine. Ill reach out.
好 我会转告肖检察官 让她等你电话的
Good, um, I'll tell DA Shaw to expect your call.
你们还好吗
Things good?
你和雷
You and Ray?
好极了
Couldn't be better.
那就好
Glad to hear it.
再次恭喜
Congratulations again.
回头见 蕾妮
See you around, Renee.
菲茨迟到了
Fitzy's late.
线人迟到正常 习惯就好
CIs are always late. Get used to it.
唇膏麦克风带了吗
Got your lipstick mic on you?
在
It's, uh
行 放包里就行
Yeah, just, um, leave it in your purse.
发生什么我都能听见
I can hear everything that's going on.
要是他们
Hey, uh, what if they
给我毒品 怎么办
uh, like, offer me`drugs?
官方说法 州警在任何情况下
Officially, state police troopers are not allowed
都不允许使用毒品
to use narcotics under any circumstances.
私底下说 我是你搭档 懂吗
Unofficially, I'm your partner, okay?
我挺你
And I got your back.
收到
终于来了
Here he is
嗨 菲茨
Hey, Fitzy.
你来晚了
You're late.
我的错 我有点
Yeah, my bad. I had some, uh,
事情需要处理
business that needed my attention.
行 所以你查到什么了
Yeah, okay. What do you got for us?
雷德正在派对上疯玩儿
Uh, Red's kicking it at a house party.
他叫我过去
He told me to come through.
那好极了 你们俩一起去
That's great, actually. You two ride together.
我跟着
I'm gonna follow.
你只需要把莎拉介绍给雷德就行
AII you gotta do is introduce Sarah to Red.
给她做个担保就行
Just be like, "She's cool. "
剩下的交给她
She'll take care of the rest.
行了 去吧
AlI right. Let's go.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 你一定就是瑞秋了
Hi. You must be Rachel.
请进 请进
Uh, come in. Come in.
太谢谢你能来了
Um, thank you so much for coming.
我是蕾妮 这是斯嘉丽
Um, I'm Renee, and this is Scarlet.
嗨蕾妮 嗨斯嘉丽
Hi, Renee. Hi, Scarlet.
我是瑞秋
I'm Rachel.
好吧 这你已经知道了
Um, you just you already know that.
啊哦
Oops.
总之 你们家真的好美
Well, anyway, what a gorgeous house.
她看上去像是葡萄汁瓶子上的小人似的
And this one could be on a grape juice bottle.
多谢
Thanks.
抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry.
我是说像广告一样很可爱
I just meant, like, those adorable ads.
好 谢谢你
Right. Yeah, thank you.
好了
Um, okay,
她10点钟睡第一觉
so she goes down for her first nap at ten.
等她醒过来之后喂一瓶奶
Uh, give her a bottle when she wakes up.
然后需要你们在三点
And then I need you guys to go pick up
去夏令营接小弗兰基
Frankie Jr. from camp at three
然后 或许可以再打扫一下
And then, um, just maybe some light cleaning.
行 没问题
Yup, no problem.
你真的帮我大忙了 我 我实在是事情太多了
You're a lifesaver. I just, uh, got a lot going on.
瞧瞧你
Well, looking at you
不管是什么事 你肯定可以解决的
whatever it is, I'm sure you can handle it.
谢谢你
Thanks
好了 那就
Okay, yeah, let's, uh- -
那就试试看吧
let's give it a shot, you know?
为什么不呢
I mean, why not?
好耶
Oh, yay.
太好了 我是认真的
Yay. And I mean it.
我是来帮忙的 所以你可以去上班了
I am here to help, so now get yourself to work.
不用担心什么
You have nothing to worry about.
对吧 根本不用担心
Right? Nothing to worry about.
好 我爱你
Okay. Okay. I love you.
好 太感谢了 瑞秋
Okay. Thanks, Rachel, so much.
和妈妈说拜拜
Bye, Mommy.
-和妈妈说拜拜  -拜
Bye, Mommy. - Bye.
和妈妈说拜拜
Bye, Mommy.
拜拜
Bye.
白垃圾
♪'White trash ♪
别这么叫我
♪ Don't call me that ♪
白垃圾
♪White trash ♪'
别这么叫我 宝贝
♪ Donlt call me that Baby ♪
你知道我爱你 宝贝
♪ You know Ilove you, baby ♪'
但你别以为
♪ But don't you think That maybe ♪
你这么跟我讲话
♪ The way you talking to me ♪
会让我生出一股寒意
♪ Would send a chill Right through me ♪
白垃圾
♪ White trash ♪
别这么叫我
♪ Don't call me that ♪
他们脑子没病吧
Are they fucking serious?
一群蠢货 开着蠢得要死的车
Dumbasses riding around in a dumbass car,
都没发现被人跟了
didn't even notice that they got followed,
让这么个乳臭未干的小鬼看管
and one Gerber Baby- ass white boy watchdogging
欧文的仓库 连把椅子都没有
Owen stash house, and he ain't even got a chair.
弗劳利叔侄实在是太粗疏了
The Frawleys are sloppy as hell.
就像是等着被抢一样
It's like they want to get took.
是啊
Yeah.
我们要抢过来
And we gonna take it.
但要用聪明办法
But we gonna take it smart.
看着我们到场
♪ See us roll up ♪
到场 马上轮到我们 他们都等不及
♪Roll up, we next They can't wait ♪
到场 我们被分开
♪ Roll up, we get tore up ♪
靠
Oh, shit.
怎么了
What?
欧文就在那边
That's Owen right over there.
我不知道他也会在
I didn't know he was gonna be here.
-嗨 雷德  -嗨
Hey, Red. Hey.
你看红袜队比赛了吗
Did you catch the Sox?
看了 马丁内斯就是个傻逼
Yeah, Martinez is a fucking retard.
-这谁  -是啊 这谁
Who's that? - Yeah, who's that?
我叫莎拉
I'm Sarah.
会走路会讲话
I even walk and talk
行 你好啊
AII right What's good, then?
我就是来过夏天的
I'm just kicking it here for the summer.
-她没问题的  -我想也是
She's cool. - No doubt.
欢迎来到鳕鱼角
Welcome to the Cape.
所以你们是怎么认识的
So how you two know each other?
小时候一起玩的
We're play cousins from when we were kids.
我们妈妈关系挺好
My mom and his are tight.
我们不是一对
We're not together.
我想也是
Yeah no shit.
要来喝杯啤酒之类的吗
Want to come have a beer or something?
行啊
Yeah. Bet.
你叫什么来着
What was your name again?
菲茨
Um, I'm Fitzy.
拜 菲茨
Bye, Fitzy.
好了
Okay. -
我的天
Oh. Oh, my goodness.
你怎么看
What do you think?
挺性感的吧
Pretty hot, huh?
他就喜欢金发蠢女人
He likes them blonde and obvious.
他就喜欢 浪货
He likes them...slutty.
-哪边  -这里
Which way It's over here.
这里比上一个强 相信我
It's better than the last place, trust me.
是这里 就在这儿
It's this one. It's right here.
起床了 小婊子
Rise and shine, bitch.
搞什么
What the fuck?
住在这里的那姑娘人呢
What happened to the girl who lived here?
我不知道
I don't know.
经理说他挺久没见她了
Manager says he hasn't seen her for a while.
她的房租也晚了4天了
She was late on her rent for four days,
所以他让我们把她东西都扔了
so he told us to throw all her stuff in the dumpster.
你扔了吗
And you did it?
是啊
Yeah.
那去你妈的
Well, fuckyou, then, bitch.
艾玛 艾玛 等等
Emma. Emma, wait.
哪里的垃圾箱
Where's the dumpster?
我的天
Oh, God.
真是气死我了
Fucking pisses me off, you know?
她以为自己谁啊 随便扔别人东西
Who the fuck is she, throwing people's shit out?
你不能随便扔别人东西的
You don't just throw people's shit out.
那都是有用的
They need their stuff.
这是她的吗
Hey, is this her stuff?
靠 对
Shit. Yeah.
我的天 小维肯定都要气死了
Oh, my God, V's gonna be so fucking pissed.
她总是喜欢把衣服熨得平平整整的
She likes to keep all her shit pressed and perfect.
我的天 这是伦坡先生
Oh, my God, that's Mr. Lumpo.
维罗妮卡的妈妈在她小时候送她的
Veronica's mom gave him to her when she was little.
怎么了
What?
没什么 你吓到我了而已
Nothing. You're just kind of freaking me out, okay?
艾玛 怎么了 告诉我
Emma, what? Tell me.
听着 我他妈都已经站在这垃圾箱里想办法找她了
Look, I don't know what else to say other than I'm standing
我不知道还能说什么了 好吗
in a fucking dumpster trying to find this girl, okay?
-我是来帮忙的 艾玛  -好 好
- I am here to help, Emma. - All right. All right.
听着 我们都知道 维罗妮卡
Look, we both know that Veronica's got
手不干净 是吧
sticky fingers, right?
她拿什么了
What'd she take?
我不知道 是个客人的东西
I don't know. Something from a trick.
我不知道她从谁那儿拿了什么 但
I don't know who or what it was, but
I don't know who or what it was, but...
那是上周的事
...that was last week.
自那之后我就没见过她了
I haven't seen her since.
斯韦齐会知道她有没有抢劫吗
Did Swayzee know if she robbed the guy?
你偷客人的东西
You lift something off a trick,
你的皮条客肯定知道
yeah, your pimp's gonna find out.
他说什么了
What'd he say?
他说他要杀了那臭婊了
He said, "I'm gonna fucking kill that cunt. "
靠
Shit.
靠 靠
Shit. Shit.
不不不
4LL BROOK Oh, no, no, no, no.
-艾玛  -你逼我跑步
Emma. - You make me run,
就要付出代价
I'll make you pay.
手放在我能看到的地方
Hands where I can see them!
-手举起来  -手放在我能看到的地方
Put your hands up. - Hands where I can see them!
手举起来
You show me your hands!
艾玛 艾玛
Emma. Emma.
赶紧的 出来
Come on. Get out of there.
这就出来 别紧张
I'm going, man. I'm going. Cool out.
手放车上
Get your hand on the car.
你 赶紧过去
You, over there right now.
行了 冷静点 我也是警察
AlI right, cool out. I'm a cop.
我冷静得很 你是警察 那你知道该怎么办
I'm cooled out. You'rea cop? Then you know what to do.
好好好
AlI right, all right, all right.
赶紧的 手放车盖上
Do it now. Hands down on the hood.
脚站开 脚站开
Spread your feet Spread your feet!
你身上有尖锐物品吗
You got any spikes on you?
没有
No, man.
要是我被扎 那就要扎回你身上
I get pricked, you get pricked.
我身上没带针
I don't have any needles.
我跟你说了 我是州警
I'm telling you, I'm state police.
这什么
What's this?
-给我  -利普曼 你看看这个
Give me thatHey, Lippman, check that out.
这什么东西
What we got here?
你们的货藏哪儿了
Where you keep your stash? Huh?
不 老兄 我们是干净的
No, no, man. We're clean.
有什么发现
What you got?
靠 麦克
Oh, shit, Mike.
完了 它被我杀了
Oh, no. I killed it. -
我该不会要去面对委员会审议了吧
Hey, thinkIm conna have to clear a board over this?
让我看看
Let me see here.
我叫杰基·奎尼奥内斯 听见了呜
My name is Jackie Quinones, all right?
我是鳕鱼角跨机构缉毒组的卧底
I'm working out of CCINU undercover
上级是雷·阿布鲁佐 行吗
under Ray Abruzzo, okay?
-等下  -你们可以去问
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. You can ask- -
你是说雷·阿布鲁佐吗
Did you say Ray Abruzzo?
我很久之前跟那混蛋搭档过
I- I did detail with that son of a bitch back- -
你们可以 放开她
you guys can- - get her off.
可以放手了
You can get your hands off of there.
没事了
You're good. -
他跟你讲过那香蕉的故事吗
Did he ever tell you the banana story?
那 那是我的故事
That- that's my story.
所以你怎么来福尔布鲁克了 杰基
So what brings you to Fall Brook, Jackie?
我在找一个性工作者 叫维罗妮卡·莱瓦伊
Uh, I'm looking for a sex worker named Veronica Levoie.
这是她最后出现的地址
This was her last known addlress.
-维罗妮卡·莱瓦伊  -对
Veronica Levoie. Huh.
我没什么印象
No, doesn't ring a bell, huh?
-你呢  -不认识
- You? - Idon'tknow her.
但我们会帮忙留意她的
We'll keep an eye out for her, though.
给你个建议 杰基
Piece of advice, Jackie.
下次记得跟警局报告
Next time, check in with the PD.
你可以说找利普曼警官
You can ask for Officer Lippman.
我会帮你的
I'l help you out.
谢了
Thanks. -
照顾好你自己
Take care of yourself.
祝你们日安
You girls have a nice day.
捡一下行吧
Pick that up, will ya?
我就知道
I fucking knew it.
我他妈就知道你是个该死的条子
I fucking knew you were a fucking cop.
抱歉我骗了你 好吗
Im sorry Iied, all right?
我只是觉得我不这么说你就不会帮我了
I just didn't think you'd help me out if- -
是啊 没错 条子去死吧
Yeah, you're fucking right, 'cause fuck the police.
-喂  -我操
Hey! - God, fuck.
艾玛 看着我 看着我
Emma, look at me. Look at me.
我会处理这件事的 好吗
I am going to take care of it, all right?
我会找到维罗妮卡的 如果是斯韦齐伤害了她
I am gonna find Veronica, and if Swayzee hurt her,
我也会处理掉他的 所以你能不能告诉我
I'm gonna take care of that too, so can you please
我去哪儿能找到斯韦齐
just tell me where I can find Swayzee?
你不是条子吗
You're the cop.
你自己查啊
You figure it out. Hmm?
行 可以
Sure. Yeah, okay.
我理解
I get it.
看看你
Look at you.
你觉得你他妈可以拯救世界
You think you can save the fucking world.
是这样吗
Is that what it is?
那你他妈的错了
Well, you're fucking wrong,
你这就是在浪费时间
and you're wasting your goddamn time.
我们只有一个晚上
♪ Uh, we got one night only ♪
拿出点实际行动来
♪ Put your money Where your mouth is ♪
因为我觉得你其实不想要
♪Cause I don't think You really want this ♪
只有一个晚上 拿出点实际行动来
♪One night only, put your Money where your mouth is...♪
塔菲到我办公室来
Taffy, my office.
但我还什么都没听到
♪But I ain't heard Nothing, yeah ♪
拿出点实际行动来
♪Put your money Where your mouth is...♪
你又要说教吗
You gonna give me another lecture?
锁门
Lock the door.
干什么
What is this?
坐下
Sit down.
我抓到你在俱乐部里贩毒
So I caught you selling in the club.
我也说了 我不希望你
AlI right, and I told you I didn't want you
在这里卖那些垃圾
peddling that shit in here.
蕾妮 我没有 我
Renee, I'm not. I-
但这些 不是垃圾
This however, isn't shit.
这是纯度达到
This, this is pure
医用水准的高纯度可卡因
pharmacy- grade fish scale cocaine.
这是你可以在这儿卖的
This you can sell in here.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you're thinking, and.
这不是陷阱
...this isn't a setup.
这是商业报价
It's a business offer.
我不明白 你之前明明
It's just, you were being a total C- unit
为了这件事烦人得要死
about it the other day
无意冒犯
No offense.
没事
None taken.
听着 这么说吧 我见过真正的大生意了
Look, let's just say that, uh, I've seen the light
我也受够了
and I am so sick of men
只能吃男人手指缝里漏下来的东西
breaking off little crumbs for us.
没错
And yeah,
我是弗兰基的女人 你知道这意味着什么吗
I was Frankie's girl, and you know what that means?
这意味着我也完全可以做这生意
That means I can do this shit as well as anyone,
所以我为什么不做呢
so why not me?
你光是靠脱衣舞和卖假货
And you're not gonna get anywhere
是赚不到什么钱的
selling lap dances and nickel bags,
那咱们就开干呗
so let's fucking do this.
你从我这儿买货 只能从我这儿
You buy from me and only me.
你可以跟别的姑娘商量好
You can work it out with the other girls
一起卖给客人
selling to customers.
不能有其他人知道我是跟你一伙的
No one else knows I'm with you.
不能欠我钱 自己吸的也要付
You're never late on my money, and you pay for what you snort.
你觉得怎么样
How does that sound?
行
Okay.
结果发现那个球童
Turns out, the batboy, right,
那个五年级的小鬼 一直在偷我们装备
this little fifth grade fuck's been pinching all our gear,
钉鞋 球 什么都偷
like, our cleats and balls and whatnot.
搞什么 你报警了吗
What the fuck? Did you call the cops?
让警察去死啊
Fuck the cops.
我和一垒手 我们把他带进浴室
Me and the first baseman, we took him in the shower
狠狠抽他丫的
and smack, smack.
我的天
Oh, my God,
你太有意思了 欧文
you're fucking hilarious, Owen.
把他脑壳敲开花了
Split his head open.
-操  -是啊
Fuck. Yeah.
你真会玩儿
You are one down chick
我就是这样的
That's how I do. Mm.
我喜欢那家伙的衣服
I like that guy's shirt.
你们是朋友吗
You friends?
听说过 那是普利莫
Word. Yeah. That's Primo.
其中一个小伙子
One of the boys.
他们俩长得有点像
Him and him, they kind of look alike.
是兄弟吗
Are they brothers?
汤米吗
Tommy?
对 他们是兄弟
Yeah, yeah, yeah, they're brothers.
他们都是跟我们一起的
They both ride with us.
你这玩意儿是哪儿来的
- Where'd you get that? -
你妈给你的吗
Did your mother give that to you?
还是你爸给你的
Father give that to you?
我妈给我的
My mother gave that to me.
杰基 怎么现在戒毒地方都能用手机了吗
Jackie, what, they got- - they got phones in rehab now?
拜托 雷 放过我吧
Oh, come on, Ray. Give me a break.
我不是已经放过你了吗
Ah, I thought I was giving you one.
听着 我在办大事 好吗
Look, Im working on something big, okay?
可能是谋杀
Like, murder big maybe.
我不知道 我只是需要你帮个忙
I don't know. Ijust need your help real guick
现在我上不去警方数据库了
I got shut out of the police database and- -
因为你现在不是警察了
That's'cause you're not currently a police officer.
听着 我只是想知道一个叫斯韦齐的
Look, I just need a last known
Look, Ijust need a last known
福尔布鲁克这边的皮条客 最后出现在哪里
on a Fall Brook pimp named Swayzee.
你滚吧
Get the fuck out of here.
雷 拜托 我真的很需要你帮这个忙
Ray, come on, man. I really need this. Please.
杰基 要是我把你需要的东西列个单子出来
Jackie, if I was making a list of things you need,
那得有100行长
it would be 100 lines long,
而且这里面绝对不包括找到这个叫斯韦齐的皮条客
and not one of them would be finding a pimp named Swayzee.
雷 我跟你说了 这很重要
Ray, Im telling you, this is important.
你听上去不太好
You just don't sound good.
我挺好 我没事
I'm good. I'm fine.
我都说了我真没事
I'm fine, man. I'm telling you.
这只是 这事儿太疯狂了
This is just it's some crazy shit.
我就是需要你帮个忙
Ijust need your help.
杰基 现在有个卧底身入险境
Jackie, I got an undercover in a dangerous situation.
我现在真的没这个时间
I just don't have time for this right now.
雷 我都没有
Ray, I didn't even- -
你照顾好自己 拜托了
Okay, so just take care of yourself, please.
雷
Ray!
操
Fuck!
Fuck
我靠 珍妮尔
Goddamn, Janelle.
你的小逼肯定湿得很吧
Bet you got that wet- wet, right?
赶紧来跟我操一把
Yo, come fuck with this woo real guick.
你他妈闭嘴吧
Yo, shut the fuck up.
怎么这么跟女士说话呢
That's no way to talk to a lady.
你他妈滚吧
Man, get the fuck out of here,
跟苍蝇似的绕着奥西托的剩菜
sniffin' around Osito's leftovers.
好了 普克
AII right, Pook.
这是你第三次了
That's your third strike.
今天给我闭嘴
You're done talking for today.
医生给你检查完了
I believe the doctor is done with you.
我可以照顾好自己 谢谢你
And I can take care of myself, thank you very much.
我跟你没什么好说的
Me and you ain't got no business, cuz.
或许你是压根没生意可做
Maybe you got no business at all.
是吧 兄弟
Huh, cuz?
我听说白人把你的顾客都抢走了
I hear the white boys took all your customers.
鬼扯 我好得很
Shit, I'm good.
不
Nah.
我觉得你不好
I don't think you are.
因为你兄弟奥西托忙着睡女人
Cause your boy Osito is too busy getting his dick wet
没空管生意
to take care of business.
珍妮尔 是吧
Janelle, right?
你他妈赶紧带着你的屁话
You need to get the fuck out of my face
有都远滚多远
with that bullshit.
让开点 奎瓦斯
Back it up, Cuevas.
现在我在这儿了
So you got me here.
然后呢
What now?
我能跟你说件事吗
Yo, can I tell you something?
就事实
Just a straight fact?
行啊 说什么都行
Yeah. Anything
你的胸太美了
Yo, your tits look amazing
我的胸
My tits Mm- hmm.
是很美
are amazing.
或许我应该亲眼看看它们
I think maybe I should see them naked, hmm?
你继续下去 说不定就有机会
Yeah, if you keep doing that, you just might.
等我一下
Give me a minute.
行吗
- Mm. Okay?
别逼我来找你
Don't make me come looking for you.
雷
Hey, Ray?
你还在外面吗
Are you still out there?
拜托告诉我 我表现得很好
Tell me I'm doing a good job.
你表现得非常好了
谢了
Thanks.
我很高兴能有你在外面
Hey, I'm glad you're out there.
让我感觉很安全
It makes me feel safe.
排骨 我是桑蒂勒警探
Chuleta, it's Detective Saintille.
客房服务
Room service.
听着 肖检察官对庭审准备
So look, DA Shaw's getting real serious
是来真的 好吗
about this trial prep shit, all right?
如果你知道任何关于豪尔赫的事情
I need you to seriously tell me
你真的 得告诉我
if you know anything about what happened to Jorge.
等一下 兄弟
Now, hold up, man.
首先 我的游戏机呢
First thing first. The fuck is my Xbox?
-游戏机  -是啊
- Xbox? - Yeah.
需要我提醒你一下 你为什么在这里吗
Do I need to remind you why you're here?
你差点就要被起诉为
You're on the hook
两起谋杀案的事后从犯了
for accessory after the fact on two bodies.
还是三起
Or is that three?
你他妈别鬼扯了
Fuck out of here with that shit.
我已经跟你们说了 弗兰基没有杀豪尔赫
I already told you Frankie didn't kill Jorge.
真的吗
Really?
那你知道会是谁
Do you have any information
杀死豪尔赫的吗
on anyone who would've killed Jorge?
不 我不知道
No, I don't
但我有个推论
but I got, like, a- a theory.
行
Okay.
说说看
Let's hear your theory.
蕾妮
Renee.
她恨透那混蛋了
She hated that motherfucker.
她看他的眼神 简直是怨毒
She looked at him with those poison eyes.
你看到蕾妮杀死豪尔赫了吗
You see Renee kill Jorge?
没有
No.
你有听到蕾妮或者别人说
You hear Renee say or anyone else say
她杀了豪尔赫吗
she killed Jorge?
没有
No.
所以你能给我的
So all you got for me.
就是她的怨毒眼神
is poison eyes.
我就这么跟你说了吧
I'm telling you.
那真是谢谢你给我这个消息
Well, I'm glad, uh, you gave me that tip.
你真他妈是给案子打开了全新的思路
You just fucking broke the case wide open.
真不知道我为什么没早点问你
Don't know why I didn't ask you sooner.
这些啤酒我拿走了
I am taking these beers back,
去你妈的游戏机
and fuck your goddamn Xbox.
该死的蠢货
Fuckin' moron.
嗨
Hey.
嗨 怎么了
Hey. What's up?
我不是要批评你
Like, uh, I don't mean to criticize,
但我刚刚看了排班表
but I was looking at the schedule.
我看到你下个月给塔菲
I saw you put Taffy on Friday and Saturday nights
排了周五周六晚上
for the next month.
赚钱的晚上
Our money nights.
是啊
Yeah. Uh- huh.
她人是挺好的
I mean, she's sweet and all,
但你不觉得她更适合午班
but don't you feel like she's more of a lunch shift,
穴
是安稳类型的吗
- "any port in a storm"type? -
拜托 我不是想刻薄什么
Come on, I'm not trying to be mean.
这对她也不好
It's bad for her too.
她不像其他姑娘那么能赚
She's not gonna earn the way the other girls do.
-我的天 你怎么了  -抱歉
Oh, my God, what's wrong? - I'm sorry.
都是该死的荷尔蒙
It's the stupid fucking hormones.
只是 有时候看着这些姑娘 我真的会伤心
It's just, sometimes it's sad looking at these girls.
她们真的得这么干才能赚到钱吗
Like, this is really what they have to do to make money?
过来 来
Come here. Come on.
没事的
It's okay.
好了 塔菲没事的
Okay, Taffy, is gonna be fine.
好吗 交给我
Okay? I got this.
你不用担心
You don't have to worry about any of it.
相信我
Trust me.
我确实相信你
I do. I do trust you.
能有你在真是太好了
God, I'm so fucking glad you're here.
肮脏的触摸为我解渴
♪Dirty touch Quench my thirst ♪
我最爱的毒药
♪ My favorite drug ♪
再来一剂
♪ One more dose ♪
再来 再来一剂
♪One more, one, one One more ♪
再来一剂
♪ One, one more dose...♪
意思就是
Yeah, the bottom line is...
-他得走人  -他得走人吗
- he's gotta go. - He's gotta go?
这他妈什么意思 怎么就得走人了
What the fuck's that supposed to mean, he's gotta go?
你他妈知道什么意思
You know what the fuck it means.
让那肥猪去死
Fuck that fat spook.
奥西托想要开打毒品大战
Osito wants a drug war.
我们还有史努比 菲尔
We got Snoopy, Phil,
让-吉尼 雷吉
Jean- Genie, Reg- -
老兄 拜托
Dog, come on.
给我打起精神来
Jeez, get some yayo in you,
突然之间你就闭不上嘴了
all of a sudden, you can't shut up.
生意可以等等
Business can wait.
生意
Business?
你是做生意的吗
You're a businessman?
别这样
Uh, don't do that.
别耍小聪明 别耍小聪明
Don't be cute. Don't be cute.
-别耍小聪明吗  -不不不
Don't be cute? - No, no, no.
这不适合你
Cute's not your thing.
你是个性感尤物
You're fucking hot. -
就是这样
That's what you are.
你好了吗
You about it, hmm?
-好了  -是吗
Yeah. Yeah?
是啊 我们走
Yeah. Let's go.
你他妈要去哪儿
Where the fuck are you going?
不
No.
好了 给我看看胸
Now, show me those fucking tits.
不
Oh, no.
我还以为你不会开口了
I thought you'd never ask.
我操 我真是操了
Fucking trick. Fuck.
真棒
Yeah, that's good.
我的天 你真是太辣了
Oh, my God, you're so fucking hot.
你真是太硬了
Oh, and you're so fucking hard.
你喜欢这个吗
Yeah. You like this right here?
真大
It's so big.
我知道 宝贝 来捏两把
I know, baby. Come here and squeeze it.
好啊
Oh, yeah.
喜欢吗
You like that?
太爽了
Feels so fucking bad, man.
没错 就是这样
Yeah, that's it.
我操
Fucking God.
我要看看你有多猛
I want to see how fucking hard you can come.
操了
Fuck me.
来吧 宝贝 让我看看
Come on, baby. Show me. Show me.
-咱来做朋友  -糟了 糟了
- Let's you and me be friends. - Oh, oh, crap. Oh, crap.
朋友 你身上有枪吗
You got a gun, friend, somewhere on your person?
左边前面口袋
Left front pocket.
完了
Oh, crap.
喂 牛奶箱 怎么了
Yo, Milkcrate...what's up?
不 不
No, no.
不不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
-不不不  -不什么
- No, no, no. No, what?
你们要杀了我
You're going to kill me.
你怎么知道
How you know that?
你们没戴面罩 所以你们要杀了我
You didn't wear masks, so you're gonna kill me.
我戴什么面罩也遮不住啊
What kind of mask is gonna hide me, hmm?
但这不代表我就不狡猾了
But that don't mean I can't be sly.
我狡猾得很
I can be sly as a motherfucker.
所以 你可以把今晚看到的事都告诉欧文
So you can tell Owen everything you saw here tonight,
也可以换个说法告诉他
or you could tell him something else.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
或许没有发生盗窃
Maybe there was no theft.
可能我们都没来过
Shit, maybe we weren't even here.
或许是你把烟扔错了地方
Maybe you threw your smokes in the wrong pile of rags
然后就
and then.
咻
poof.
如果我告诉欧文 所有货都被烧了
If I tell Owen the whole stash burned in a fire,
他会打死我的
he will beat my ass.
是 但如果你告诉他 我们把货都抢走了
Yeah, but if you tell him we took down the stash,
他一样会打死你
he's gonna beat your ass too,
所以无论如何
So either way,
你今晚都是要被打死的
you getting your ass beat tonight.
但按我的来 我们分你一块 照顾你一下
But my way, we slide you a brick for your trouble.
你告诉欧文这里出了火灾
You tell Owen there was a fire.
他揍你一顿
He does the Riverdance on your ass.
你还能赚三万块
You spend your 30 Gs.
那
Well- -
快点 你想太久了
Hurry up, man. You're taking too long.
你怎么知道我不会拿你们东西
How- how do you know I won't take a brick
然后还是告诉欧文呢
and tell Owen anyway?
因为这样的话 我就会杀了你
Cause then I will fucking kill you.
嗨 不好意思
Hey. Excuse me.
嗨 你好
Hi. How are you?
你不是客人 我也没这个时间
You're not a trick, and I don't have the time.
我只是 我只是有些问题想问
I just- - I just want to ask some questions.
你问 我不一定回答
You can ask. Don't mean I'ma answer.
我只是在找一个叫斯韦齐的皮条客
Um, I'm just trying to find out about this pimp Swayzee.
你认识他
So you know him.
你是他的人吗
You work for him?
我是自己的人 我已经在这儿30年了
I work for myself. I been out here 30 years.
我自己赚钱自己花
I make my own money, and I buy my own junk.
你知道我去哪儿能找到他吗
You know where I can find him?
皮条客不是能被你找到的 姑娘
You don't find pimps, girl.
是他们来找你
They find you.
信赖信任
Trust and believe.
那你认不认识他手底下的姑娘
Do you know any of the girls
比如一个叫维罗妮卡的
who work for him, like a Veronica?
你觉得我认识这儿所有接客的姑娘吗
You think I know every girl in this town turning a trick?
得了吧
Bitch, please.
好吧 听着
Okay, look, um
这个姑娘是他手底下的
there's this girl that works for him,
她现在失踪了
and she's been missing.
我真的很担心她 你见过她吗
I'm really worried about her. You seen her?
怎么了
What?
有人来找的显然是白女
Of course you be out here looking for a white girl.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你在找杀死玛克辛·麦克莱恩的凶手吗
Are you looking for who killed Maxine McLean
或者是另外那些再也没有出现过的姑娘
or any of the other girls that's been good and gone?
不
No.
白女错过一次约会
White girl miss one appointment,
就开始大肆找人了 是吧
and you call out the dogs, huh?
等下 等下
Hold- hold on. Hold on.
玛克辛·麦克莱恩是谁
Who's- who's Maxine McLean?
你自己查去吧
Google it, bitch.
艾玛 是我做错了 好吗
Emma, I made a mistake, okay?
我不该骗你的 但这事儿真的很糟糕
I shouldn't have lied to you, but this shit is fucked,
我觉得你是唯一一个能帮我找到维罗妮卡的人
and I think you're the only one who can help me find Veronica.
算了 我操 我这就过去
You know what? Fuck it. I'm coming over.
艾玛
Emma?
Hey, Emma.
瞧瞧这他妈是谁
Oh, look who the fuck it is. -
操 你他妈给我放手
Fuck. Get your fucking hands off me.
-闭嘴  -艾玛
Shut up. Emma.
闭嘴 闭嘴 你这个多管闲事的臭婊子
Shut up. Shut up, you nosy little fucking bitch.
你吓不到我
You don't scare me.
我当然吓得到你
Oh, yes, I fucking do.
你不告诉我维罗妮卡怎么了
I'm not going anywhere
我哪儿也不会去的
till you tell me what happened to Veronica.
我跟你说了 我他妈不认识什么维罗妮卡
I told you I don't know any fucking Veronicas.
真有意思 因为我听说你说过 要杀了那臭婊子
Funny, cause I heard you said you were gonna kill that cunt.
然后呢
That what happened?
我不认识那个婊子
I don't know that bitch,
但我了解她那种婊子
but here's what I know about bitches like her.
她那种婊子 都他妈是小偷
Bitches like her, they're all fucking thieves.
她那种婊子
Bitches like her,
能碰到什么就偷什么
they take whatever they can get their hands on.
然后换来毒品扎针嗑嗨
They shoot it in their skinny fucking arms.
她那种婊子 每一个
And bitches like her end up fucking dead
都是走死路
every single time.
所以你的意思是 她偷了嫖客的东西
So what you're saying is, she stole something from a john
然后卖了换钱
and sold it for drugs.
她会卖给谁
Who'd she sell it to?
别他妈给我多管闲事
Stay out of my fucking business.
我跟你说过一次了
I told you once.
下一次 就不是这种方式了
Next time, I'm gonna tell you a different way.
现在 给我滚出去
Now, get the fuck out.
操
Fuck.
怎么了
What's up?
靠
Oh, shit.
欧文 牛奶箱打来的
Owen, that was Milkcrate.
我们的仓库出大问题了
We- we got a big fucking problem at the stash house.
-什么  -我们得走了
- What? - We gotta go.
操 走 我们走
Fuck. Come on. Come on. Let's go.
我回头打给你
I'll call you.
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck happened?
你他妈把这儿烧了吗
What, did you light the fucking place up?
是个意外
It was an accident.
我只是掉了烟
I swear I just dropped my smoke.
你他妈蠢货
Stupid motherfucker!
还在里面吗
Is it in there? Hmm?
东西还在里面吗 给我进去拿
Is the stuff still in there? Go get it.
都烧掉了
It's all burned up.
你他妈给我进去拿 不然我弄死你
Go fucking get it, or I will fucking kill you!
欧文 求你了
Owen, please.
八块 这就够了
Eight bricks. That'll do.
通知弗农等包裹
Let Vernon know he can expect a package.
告诉街上的小伙子们 准备起来以防万一
Tell the boys in the street, start toolin' up just in case.
我得问一句
I gotta say,
如果我们要开战
now, if we going to war,
整这么麻烦干什么
why go through all this?
为什么不直接告诉他们
Why not let'em know what's up?
烧掉那里就意味着 就算他们知道是我们干的
Burning it down means even if they know we robbed them,
也不知道货在我们手里
they don't know.
玩儿心理战是吧
Like some psychological warfare shit.
所以你才是管事儿的
Hey, yo, that's why you the boss.
咱们再待会儿
Let's chill for a minute.
我喜欢这味道
I like the way that smells.
你准备说什么吗
Are you gonna say anything?
你要我说什么
What do you want me to say?
我都不知道
You know what? I'm not even too sure
上面发生了什么
what happened up there.
我打进内部了
I'm on the inside.
这不是你想要的吗
Isn't that what you wanted?
你行动第二天就和目标上了床
You had sex with a target on day two of an operation.
你知道这有多离谱吗
Do you know how fucked up that is?
-你不也和蕾妮睡了吗  -立刻给我住嘴
- You had sex with Renee. - Whoa, stop that right now.
-为什么  -那不一样
- Why? - That's- that's different.
为什么 因为我是女的吗
Why? Because I'm a chick?
而且我没跟他睡
Besides, I didn't fuck him.
他只是在打飞机 所以我用手帮了他一把
He was jerking off, so I helped him with my hand a little.
要是我跟他睡了 那他马上就会把我扔了
If I fucked him he'd be done with me.
现在他想要更多
Now he wants more.
我听了自己的直觉
I used my instincts.
我也没有做什么自己不愿意的事情
And I didn't do anything I didn't want to.
我还搞到了一些不错的消息 是吧
And I got some pretty good intel, right?
是
Sure.
你说过你会支持我 我可以相信你
Look, you said you'd back me up, that I could trust you.
那都是鬼扯嘛
Was that bullshit?
不 不是的
No, it's not.
我永远在
I got you.
所以史密斯警长会听到今晚的录音吗
So will Lieutenant Smith hear the tape from tonight?
不
No.
如果我标记为不相关内容
No, if I label it as non- pertinent,
就不会有人听到
no one's gonna hear it.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你要进来喝一杯吗
Hey, want to come in and have a beer?
我得回家了
I gotta get home.
那回头见
See you, then.
喜欢吗
You like that?
太爽了
Feels so fucking bad, man.
没错 就是这样
Yeah, that's it.
我操
Fucking God.
我要看看你有多猛
I want to see how fucking hard you can come.
操了
Fuck me.
来吧 宝贝 让我看看
Come on, baby. Show re. Show me.
喂 彼得
Yo, Petey.
该死的 彼得 开门 我有事儿问你
God damn it, Petey, open up. I gotta ask you something.
彼得 喂 彼得
Petey. Hey, Petey.
喂 维罗妮卡有没有卖给你什么
Yo, did Veronica sell you some- -